Othniel Charles Marsh Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1854-1899; Series II
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1872; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1096., 001442
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1103., 001449
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1900; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1104., 001450
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1107., 001453
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1110., 001456
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1112., 001458
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1893-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1117., 001463
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1118., 001464
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1133., 001479
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1135., 001481
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1139., 001485
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1140., 001486
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1146., 001492
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1147., 001493
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1148., 001494
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-1896, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1149., 001495
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1152., 001498
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1153., 001499
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1156., 001502
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1160., 001506
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1162., 001508
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1163., 001509
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1870; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1164., 001510
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1166., 001512
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1878, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1167., 001513
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1898-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1168., 001514
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1171., 001517
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1178., 001524
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1862-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1181., 001527
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1183., 001529
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1189., 001535
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1898-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1192., 001538
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1193., 001539
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1195., 001541
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1200., 001546
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1868; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1201., 001547
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1202., 001548
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1866-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1206., 001552
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1210., 001556
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1884; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1214., 001560
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1216., 001562
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1217., 001563
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1218., 001564
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1898-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1228., 001574
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1229., 001575
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1230., 001576
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1235., 001581
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1236., 001582
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1238., 001584
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1240., 001586
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-187?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1244., 001590
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1245., 001591
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1248., 001594
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1251., 001597
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1872; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1253., 001599
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1255., 001601
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1257., 001603
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1260., 001606
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1261., 001607
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1894; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1263., 001609
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1264., 001610
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1265., 001611
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1879; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1268., 001614
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1269; unfinished - John D. Parker, the Mudge obituary author, lived in Knasas City in 1889/90. Is this the same Parker who wrote to Marsh? Check Marsh correspondence. - tentatively assumed to be the same, if not, create new record for the non-correspondent MAT 14/11/2012., 001615
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1270., 001616
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1879; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1271., 001617
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1274., 001620
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1275., 001621
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1279., 001625
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-1894; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1280., 001626
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1868, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1285., 001631
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1294., 001640
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as photocopies and/or typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1877-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1297., 001643
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1305., 001651
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1306., 001652
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1307., 001653
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1312., 001658
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1316., 001662
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1862-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1318., 001664
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1320., 001666
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1893-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1321., 001667
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1322., 001668
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1323., 001669
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1325., 001671
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1326., 001672
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1329., 001675
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1336., 001682
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1344., 001690
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1873, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1345., 001691
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1347., 001693
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1351., 001697
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1352., 001698
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=18179-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1354., 001700
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1357., 001703
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1361., 001707
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1891-1899, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1370., 001716
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1378., 001724
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1382., 001728
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1385., 001731
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1386., 001732
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1882; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1390., 001736
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1391., 001737
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1394., 001740
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1397., 001743
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1399., 001745
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1405., 001751
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1407., 001753
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1897-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1408., 001754
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1865-1867; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1409., 001755
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1876, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1420., 001766
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1425., 001771
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1890-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1428., 001774
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1429., 001775
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1430., 001776
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1432., 001778
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1433., 001779
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-189?, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1436., 001782
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1438., 001784
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1445., 001791
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1446., 001792
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1872; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1447., 001793
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1449., 001795
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1887, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1451., 001797
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1452., 001798
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1453., 001799
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1867; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1457., 001803
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1861-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1460., 001806
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1465., 001811
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1893-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1475., 001821
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1480., 001826
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1873-1883, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1483., 001829
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1485., 001831
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1872-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1490., 001836
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1863-1865; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1493., 001839
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1498., 001844
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1504., 001850
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1505., 001851
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1508., 001854
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1865-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1515., 001861
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1864-1865; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1519., 001865
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1520., 001866
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1521., 001867
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1899, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1525., 001871
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1526., 001872